[
    {
        "question" : "Saturn is the ________ planet from the Sun.",
        "answers"   : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Fifth" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Sixth" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Seventh" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Eighth" }
        ],
        "correct"  : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which of the following items was owned by the fewest U.S. homes in 1990?",
        "answers"   : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Home Computer" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Cordless Phone" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "CD Player" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Dishwasher" }
        ],
        "correct"  : 2
    },
    {
        "question" : "The first black American pictured on a U.S. postage stamp was who?",
        "answers"   : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Joe Louis" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Booker T. Washington" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Louis Armstrong" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Frederick Douglass" }
        ],
        "correct"  : 0
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which of these characters turned 40 years old in 1990?",
        "answers"   : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Bugs Bunny" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Charlie Brown" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Mickey Mouse" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Fred Flintstone" }
        ],
        "correct"  : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which of the following hands ranks highest in Texas Hold'em Poker?",
        "answers"   : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Full House" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Flush" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Straight" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Three of a Kind" }
        ],
        "correct"  : 0
    },
    {
        "question" : "In what year did Topps start producing baseball cards?",
        "answers"   : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "1945" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "1951" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "1954" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "1962" }
        ],
        "correct"  : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "What was the name of the island King Kong was discovered on, in the original 1933 movie?",
        "answers"   : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Ape Island" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Kong Island" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Skull Island" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Monster Island" }
        ],
        "correct"  : 2
    },
    {
        "question" : "The Philadelphia mint started putting a 'P' mint mark on quarters in what year?",
        "answers"   : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "1965" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "1970" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "1976" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "1980" }
        ],
        "correct"  : 3
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which of the following countries does not border Israel?",
        "answers"   : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Saudi Arabia" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "Jordan" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Egypt" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Syria" }
        ],
        "correct"  : 0
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which of these nations has never finished third (overall) in a FIFA World Cup?",
        "answers"   : [
            { "id" : 0, "text" : "Chile" },
            { "id" : 1, "text" : "United States" },
            { "id" : 2, "text" : "Poland" },
            { "id" : 3, "text" : "Uruguay" }
        ],
        "correct"  : 3
    }
]
